Usage: firebase firestore:delete [options] [path]

delete data from a Cloud Firestore database

Options:
  -r, --recursive          if set, recursively delete all documents and
                           subcollections at and under the specified level. May
                           not be passed along with --shallow
  --shallow                delete only documents at the specified level and
                           ignore documents in subcollections. This action can
                           potentially orphan documents nested in
                           subcollections. May not be passed along with -r
  --all-collections        deletes all collections and documents in the
                           Firestore database
  -f, --force              automatically accept all interactive prompts
  --database <databaseId>  Database ID for database to delete from. "(default)"
                           if none is provided.
  -h, --help               display help for command
